[Music]
[Applause]
i
am eating my feelings this is a very
depressing eating show today i have
pizza i'm gonna eat for you guys
this was not part of the plan the plan
was for me to drink talk about dicks
and eat
dude always makes you feel better
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hey nicota avocado daniel molly
guacamole nice to meet you nice to meet
you thanks for meeting me at the
complimentary hampton inn breakfast
buffet are you staying here
that's what these robes are for
you know i don't think we're supposed to
be sitting at the buffet
why because they don't sit at the buffet
a buffet is a bar
you can sit at a bar i guess but why do
we have to be here so early
because that's when the buffet is at its
hottest that's hamptonality
get you some forks here you go all right
where are you from i'm from columbia are
you really from columbus no
no i live there with my husband hold on
let me have try some of these eggs
explain to me what mukbanging is it's
actually mukbang it comes from korea
and that sounds racist no mukbang
you say it like it's kind of racist i'm
saying it how they pronounce it
mukbang like if you go to france you say
i'm in france you don't say french
so if i'm in china i say i'm in china is
what you're saying
the word means eating broadcast the idea
was that they put their camera down
they filmed themselves eating and then
other people would eat with them
when you jerk off it seems sexual
some people do that but that's not my
target audience you're getting millions
of views
i know but not for do you
want syrup on a pancake sure
that's plenty of syrup you didn't have
to syrup the tongs
i noticed in the beginning of your
videos you look a little bit smaller
it's nice to be here and i'm going to be
doing this a lot more regularly now
oh yeah i've gained like 50 pounds this
isn't healthy
i know it's not let's figure out a way
to do this oh my god
what about the amount of food why is it
so much well
i mean it doesn't have to be a lot but i
like to eat a lot just because
no but you're eating an unhealthy amount
you wouldn't eat that much in a normal
sitting moment
no no no no right so why are you doing
it that amount of food because it's a
great excuse to get fat
how many videos are you posting a week i
post like five days a week
five mukbang sessions a week you're
going to die i know
you're getting full already literally
getting full already you would never be
able to do this no i wouldn't
i would be for like the premature
ejaculator muck bankers
get hot you get the food sweat by the
way why are you always crying in your
videos
are you that emotional i am well the
food doesn't help either oh because you
just feel gross well you feel like
but then also like
you're just it throws your hormones out
of whack and i'm already naturally
really emotional
so i just sometimes i cry what the
was wrong with that alfredo pizza you
were eating the one in colombia
yeah it was big and it was flat cheese
looked hard
was i crying yeah yeah you were of
course you were crying it tastes better
than it looked
hey let me grab one of those this yeah
here
that's raw waffle batter isn't that bad
for you
raw waffle batter i thought this was a
waffle smoothie
tell me about how this has affected your
poops are they enormous
yes but people think i eat all the
time well
just a mukbang how long after one
of your videos
before uh-oh it's usually immediate it's
immediate
yeah and it's not the food i'm eating
it's whatever is there that gets pushed
down
is it diarrhea or is it solid if i eat
something that's
really really spicy then that hurts yeah
you said your bottle bleeds a lot it
doesn't bleed but it hurts
these fire noodles i'm obsessed with
they really make my a-hole bleed
excuse me not believe just sting sting
like a wasp
why fire noodles they're popular running
low on
eggs here if it wasn't popular the
korean fire noodle challenge i would not
be on the toilet crying twice a week
good eggs are on the bottom
hey what's up with a bird you shouldn't
let your bird eat that food that's bad
for them
i know but his name's mr noodle just
cause his name is mr noodle doesn't mean
he should eat noodles okay you caught me
no one is gonna tell you that feeding
your bird hot noodles is a good idea
well you know they can't feel spice they
can't they don't have spice receptors
i didn't know that yeah never mind go
ahead and feed them
why do you get hot sauce in your eyes so
much
i have no idea why that happens i'm just
doing my video
and hot sauce splatters into my eyeball
every time every time you want me to
tell you why it's happening
why because you can sit so low if you
had a taller chair
maybe your eyes would be out of harm's
way i don't know i think i need to get
goggles from now on
can i pass me the uh that orange juice
please
how long have you been married um a year
and a half hey everybody look who i'm
with
the husband you still kiss or do you
skip that
no because what is this a mukbang gang
bang
easy spitfire we need some of these
hey peggy these pancakes already got
syrup on them
that's hamptonality that guy's doing the
heavy lifting for us
real piece of you seem to be
riddled with diseases but they're all
self-diagnosed so i'm calling
i don't know why i'm in so much pain and
i don't want to go to a doctor because i
have a phobia
you said in your videos that you have
chronic coughing syndrome
diabetes kidney failure okay i thought i
had kidney failure i
actually turned out not to okay and i
thought that i had diabetes i actually
turned out not to too
you eat that uh that durian fruit oh i
love durian that smells like
it it does actually my best friend used
to say it smells like indian food
wrapped in a diaper try to eat some dirt
it looks like a pastry on camera they
thought it was dough
it's so good what's it what's the
texture like it's kind of like
scrambled eggs is there any danger
outside of just unhealthy eating there
is a lot of haters actually that's one
of the sole reasons as to why i have a
lot of issues
like they really get to me of course
they do you have haters right um
what makes you sad today
i don't know i just sometimes when i'm
done a mukbang i feel full and then i
just
i think about all the stuff in my life
and i get sad are you gonna cry
no maybe
you want to hug it out
[Music]
break it up boys it's 10 a.m breakfast
is over but we're still mukbanging
it's okay i brought to go boxes
all right nick cotto avocado let's go
rinse off in the pool
all
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm going right show you how us dancers
stay in shape
we're going to work today our lower body
our legs specifically especially the
[Music]
legs
don't tell me you don't have 15 minutes
a day to spend on yourself
[Music]
i love you
jill welcome to wrinkles the only gym
designed specifically for women
how do i say this nicely
past their prime hard hard to get an
erection
without medication shall i say
i can help you you can help me this is
my specialty
i think you would be a perfect addition
to our training staff but first
i have to ask you a few questions jill
is that okay okay sure how old are you
i'm 52 years old how much do you win
109. what's the most you've ever weighed
in your life 124.
and did you keep the child
lilith took it away okay i don't know
what you just said
uh finish this sentence 50 is
the new 20 20.
i like that very unrealistic
what's been your most popular workout
video i did a 10 minute
lower body workout oh yeah
six
better body you or madonna i have to
save me
although she tries but i think i can
help her too actually if you can get her
in here
let me tell you something the
celebrities that have walked through
this door
goldie hawn tiffany cherio terry brett
butler beyonce's
aunt hey leonie victoria jackson
condoleezza rice
quite regularly demi moore oh okay
beautiful woman she is
25 years ago on your youtube channel you
do a lot of
dance tributes
the character that i created is the
mother chick because
the original rock video that i did which
is in 1988
was for a band called danzig and the
song is called mother
that was you in the video in 1988 it was
pulled from mtv
because the content was considered
satanic legally i have to ask you this
are you a devil worshiper uh part-time
i am part-time you know i have to
keep a balance in my life in my
spiritual realm
the yin-yang you're a gym person yes on
martial arts
and that is blacklight like dark good
evil
i think lucifer has gotten a bad rap
that's for sure kind of set up you know
he being the light bearer
is the one that reveals truth and
uh satan is actually the one that keeps
people in the dark
what do you think of scientologists
don't say anything
i want you to introduce to the world my
latest fitness craze i'm
calling it crotch fit four intense
stages
stage one stretching the stage two
high weight low reps on the stage three
confusing the stage
four and this is the most important one
violently shaking
you guessed it get you a uniform oh
that's what everyone wears no stretchy's
going into this i'll tell you oh my lord
oh yeah that is insanity that you're
that love
are men intimidated by you i guess some
are
first of all i'm blessed genetically
well that's obvious and
it's the answer talk about the drugs
what drones
talk about the drugs stand behind me
gently put your feet in my hands you're
gonna grab my feet for balance
are you gonna lift me up one two three
oh now we hook oh and then you pull
or i pull see oh you feel it
okay you're very strong very strong
this stage is crucial pushing your body
past its comfort zone
did you see that why is that happening
is it because i've never worked out in
my life
put your arms straight down somebody
help me we're like two old bats just
hanging here
hey what's the best concert you've ever
gone to david cassidy
how are you doing right now somebody
help ah
this is the lovely tiffany our twerk
instructor
i taught her everything she knows you're
getting a lot better and i still got it
anyway for our final phase of crotch fit
we're gonna combine the love of 80s
music and drugs with
twerking i'm calling it tweaking
i never heard of it but i'll give it a
[Music]
shot
[Applause]
[Music]
like that she's a natural yeah i think
we found your calling
welcome to wrinkles
on the bong road
on the ballroom
[Music]
all right i'm the pot doctor
says you're from australia don under
came here to start a weed church yeah
mate i'm here to spread the good word
about the benefits of marijuana
sure you are potheads have no
follow-through first things first
you need a medical marijuana license to
get high in california
all right first questions i ask all my
patients
are you a cop i'm the bonelord okay have
you ever felt any of the following
symptoms
anxiety yes okay mild headaches
yes occasionally bored yes having
trouble sleeping past
noon yes can't eat an entire bag of
doritos in one sitting
yes haven't laughed once while watching
the goldbergs
yes ever sneezed trimmed a fingernail
too short do you lose patience preparing
food in a microwave
yes do you want to watch cosmos without
retaining
any information yes okay
i'm the bonelord how long have you been
the bong lord
i've been in the bonglord for my entire
life you were born the bong lord yes
well that's andre is your mother a
virgin oh
no no okay i didn't know like if it was
like the second coming of jesus christ
you know never mind it's a long story
it's a good book though
ah how old were you the first time you
smoked marijuana
15 my first time 15. did you like it
your first time
yes do your parents call you the bowling
lord
no no clue do you live with your parents
yeah
you live right under their roof and they
have no idea you're the bong lord no
basically living a double identity oh
like a superhero
yeah why did you start drinking bong
water
because it tastes good it tastes that
tastes disgusting
it's a waste and waste of pot if i don't
so you actually get high off the bong
water
hmm not too sure you're not too sure
you just don't want to waste any pot
yeah that's what the bong lord teaches
us
yes that no pot should be wasted none
whatsoever
favorite thing to eat while you're high
tacos definitely
tacos are you mexican no no
okay you ever go skiing no i've
never been you should try skiing you got
the mask
all right what's your most popular video
my most popular video is the foreshadow
your second video was the als ice bucket
challenge with a twist
do you support causes close to your
heart
yes like what it's like so
saving the children you smoke pot to
save the children
is that a thing are you high right
now on the bonelord
[Applause]
hi there my name is ken tamplin
hey
would you like to have that kind of
vocal power range
clarity and pitch well you can come join
me
kentamplinvocalacademy.com and i'll show
you how we can do it
cute top ken you're telling me that ken
tamplin can teach me to sing like ken
tamplin yeah right
when it comes to pure entertainment i'm
the best in the biz
triple threat acting piss-poor
uh dancing i'm a dude no thank you
singing i've had no training tell you
what let's see how much range you got
okay
first things first what kind of shampoo
do you use
is it true that anyone can learn to sing
pretty much almost anyone can learn to
sing
[Music]
okay cool other than being tone deaf
usually larger people can sing better
but in this case
um you have really nice bright timbre oh
cool keep it right when you come down
that sounds like a dying dog too this
sound that he's using
will destroy the voice
cool you just hold your breath when you
speak and you learn to control and
mitigate the air
hold your breath when you speak that's
right and do not stop holding your
breath
until you are out of oxygen nope you can
take a quick breath
you can take quick breaths in between
i'm running out nope look i'm out
all right so that is good i think we're
ready
and on his farm wait is it
on his farm well then why are some
people not singing that right
on that i have on that i am on this i
have
one his i want it and on that storm he
had wolves
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i'm a cop
and on that farm he had ken
[Music]
[Applause]
kampling
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
taken you want to come in right
now
yes okay i would like to come in right
i hope you bring this lock wow
you want to change all of those chips
okay twenty five hundred seventy five
hundred
twelve thousand five hundred okay
twenty four thousand one hundred and
ninety nine luck
what's the table men that's five dollars
okay
this is your bed all right good luck
oh that's not good at all
okay
[Music]
oh
okay green light so say your foot
all right you want to hit because
17. you want to hit yes please okay
15. i'm going to take a hit
now no good all right
hey
[Music]
i am sorry cocktails
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
that's a weeping mother using vr
technology to reunite
with her dearly departed daughter i'm
starting to feel
like this season might be a real bummer
even i think this is majorly effed up
and i just dumped my dog's ashes on an
audience member
sorry about that these tech companies
are profiting
off grieving parents and millions of
people online are watching this
okay just when i thought this video
couldn't get any more depressing
there's a birthday party for two it's
virtual reality you could have created
anything
at least drawn a few friends
a bounce house maybe a pony
[Music]
all right ride's over if you want to
play again you have to lose another
loved one
i called next
[Music]
daniel my favorite grandchild hop hop
is that really you leroy
jenkins
you're going down your races try hard
hey you know one of my dead relatives
well i'm here for the grandpa gangbang
sorry to tell you but he's dead again
it's not gonna stop me
this game is a lot sadder than i thought
it would be
[Applause]
[Music]